I have a message for my country and I want you to pray with me.
After the message, you join me in prayer.
This is three times I'm having this message.
Now I want to say it, it is the third time.
Yes.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The president's heart is like a stream of water in the hands of God.
Are you with me?
The president's, leader's heart is like a stream of water in the hands of God
and He can control it wherever He wants.
The first time I had the dream, I prayed and fasted on my own.
the second time again, I prayed and fasted,
But this third time, you must join me in prayer.
First, second, third.
When something is like that, you can imagine what - something strange.
So, you must join me in prayer because two believers are better than one.
For some time after my message to the nation that I am seeing us in the valley,
and our future is crying for help, since that time I keep to myself.
I should not go beyond God; I should go before Him.
The Lord said to me that I should tell the nation and leaders
to pray against the interruption of the democratic practice.
Pray against the interruption of democratic practice.
You have to join me in prayer for the nation.
The Lord gave me the prayers to offer as well
because in this case, there must be prayers given to you.
What are the prayers?
1. The Lord should give our leaders greater understanding of God's heart.
2. The Lord should give them the understanding and discretion to guide their hearts.
3. Give them understanding that will protect them and wisdom that will rescue them.
These are the prayers. Lift up your voice,
Lord Jesus, give them greater understanding of God's heart. Prayer!
Greater understanding of God's heart!
Discretion to guide their hearts! Prayer!
Understanding to protect them!
Wisdom and understanding to rescue them!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
[Amen]!
Thank you for joining me in prayer.
That is the voice of God.
The president's heart is like a stream of water in the hands of God
and He can control it wherever He wants.
Thank you. You may be seated
TT: Ndinagwe Mwakigonja
RV: Mel Flowers 07/07/2018